bermudayellowpages.bm 2012-12-19

# Bermuda Yellow Pages | Bermuda Yellow Pages Limited - Privacy Policy

Bermuda Yellow Pages Limited (BYP) is committed to protecting your personal privacy.

BYP subscribes to the provisions of the Standard for Electronic Transactions issued under the Electronic Transactions Act 1999. The BYP Privacy Policy outlines the type of information that is collected by BYP on the Site, and how it is used and protected. The BYP Privacy Policy also tells you what to do if you do not want personal Information collected when visiting the Site.

**What information do we collect?**  
When you visit the Site, you may provide BYP with two types of information:

  * Anonymous statistics collected as you browse the Site; and
  * Personal information that you knowingly give to BYP.

You can be assured that BYP does not collect personal information about you from the Site unless you provide it to BYP, therefore, you can visit the Site without telling BYP who you are or revealing personally identifiable information about yourself.

The anonymous statistics collected by BYP include details such as which pages are viewed, which browsers people use when visiting the Site, how many people visit the Site and from which domains people come. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

**Collecting information and Cookies**  
Browsing BYP’s website is generally done anonymously. BYP does not generally collect personal information when you merely browse. We do automatically collect the type of computer and operating system you are using.

Like most web sites, BYP uses "Cookie" technology in order to improve online services to you. Cookies are small files consisting of a string of text that a website can send to your internet browser. These small files identify your browser so that the Web Site can recognize you as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have set while browsing the Site. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your email address.

BYP also lets third parties that place advertisements on this Web Site use cookies. Any third party advertiser’s use of cookies is subject to that party’s own privacy practices and not this one.

On occasion BYP may use a “clear gif” or “click-through URL.” (Click-throughs). When you click one of these Click-throughs, you will pass through BYP’s Site before being delivered to your destination website. Click-throughs are tracked by BYP to help us determine your interests and measure the effectiveness of our service to you.

You have the option of setting your browser to disable cookies. This may, however, impair your ability to use the Web Site.

When visitors supply personal information about themselves to YP for a specified purpose, YP uses the information for that purpose only.

BYP may use e-mail to respond to visitors’ e-mails or to send information that a visitor has requested. BYP also uses an opt-in e-mail mailing list for promotions. E-mail addresses entered using the e-join button on the Web Site are added to the list. If you receive an unwanted e-mail from BYP, you can unsubscribe by: clicking on the "unsubscribe" link on the e-mail and following the instructions, or contacting YP at [gtaylor@bermudayp.com](mailto:gtaylor@bermudayp.com) and requesting removal from the list, or contacting BYP at Tel +1 (441) 297-YELL or Fax +1 (441) 296-0216 and requesting removal from the list.

**Why we collect personal information**  
When BYP collects and uses personal information from you, we do so to provide you enhanced service, access to our products and services, and improve and broaden the range of products services available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to provide you with information we think would be of interest or value to you. This may occasionally include information from other companies about products and services. We may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in quality control or other market research surveys with the goal of improving customer satisfaction and developing better products and services.

**When we disclose personal information**  
Any personal information, such as your name or e-mail address, that you provide to BYP through the Web Site, will not be sold or shared with third parties other than companies affiliated with BYP and its service providers unless you specifically authorize it or unless required by law. BYP may share non-personally identifiable information that it collects through the Web Site with third parties other than companies affiliated with BYP and its service providers in order to assess the results of a promotion, event or third party relationship, to provide information to current or prospective customers or to enhance your online experience.

At times, BYP may be required by law or other legal process to disclose personal information about you. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.

**How to protect your personal information**  
BYP urges you to take every precaution possible to protect your personal information when you use the Internet. BYP recommends changing your passwords often and to use a secure internet browser. Good choices for passwords include combinations of letters and numbers and upper and lower case.

This BYP Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

Bermuda Yellow Pages Limited, 26 Victoria Street Hamilton HM 12 Bermuda.
